<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>

    <string name="first_description">
        \nThis app has the purpose of guiding the users to the destination they want to reach  inside the University Alexandru Ioan Cuza.
        The functionality of the app is to display on the user\'s phone screen navigation instructions generated by scanning QR codes wich are
        placed in different locations inside the University.</string>

    <string name="instructions"><font face= "serif"><big><b>Navigation steps</b></big>\n\n<b>Step 1:</b> First you need  to go to the menu page then select \'Choose building\' and pick the one corresponding to your location \n<b>Step 2:</b> Enter your location either by text or scanning a QR code\n<b>Step 3:</b> You  have to type in your destination.\n<b>Step 4:</b> Hit the button Start Navigation.\n<b>Step 5:</b> Follow the instructions that show up on your phone screen until the next check point that you have to scan which will be mentioned in the indications.\n<b>Step 6:</b> When you reach your destination a message will appear. \n\n<big><b>Themes</b>\n\n</big>On the menu page you have an option called \'Change Theme\' which allows you to choose the theme you want to apply.\n</font>

    </string>
    <string name="help"><big><b><font  face= "serif">ASSISTANCE</font></b></big></string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="FII">UAIC, Corp C</string>

    <string name="prefs_theme_key">theme</string>

    <string name="w1">L</string>
    <string name="w2">M</string>
    <string name="w3">M</string>
    <string name="w4">J</string>
    <string name="w5">V</string>

    <string name="close_button">This closes the camera and sends you to the main screen.</string>
    <string name="next_button">This button will show you the next instruction.</string>
    <string name="previous_button">This button will show you the previous instruction.</string>
    <string name="flash_button">This will open your camera flash.</string>
    <string name="scan_button">This will allow you to scan a waypoint.</string>
    <string name="error_message">Could not load data from database. Please try refreshing the page.</string>
    <string name="end_navigation_message">You have reached your destination! Do you want to go back to the main screen?</string>
</resources>
